SURMA: How old are you?
瑟玛：你几岁？
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]
That's what my partner does.
那是我的伴侣所做的。
I'm like-- I'm playing Zelda.
我就像-我在玩《塞尔达传说》。
And then I'm done.
然后我完成了。
And I stand up and make some stupid joke.
我站起来，开个愚蠢的玩笑。
And he's like, you're 29, mate.
他就像，你29岁，队友。
JAKE: (LAUGHING) Ha, No.
杰克：（笑）哈，没有
No, no, no.
不不不。
Farts are still funny.
放屁仍然很有趣。
[THEME SONG]
[主题曲]
So.
所以。
SURMA: So.
苏尔玛：所以。
JAKE: The official starting word of any HTTP203 episode.
杰克：任何HTTP203情节的正式起始词。
SURMA: I thought I would do some code this time.
SURMA：我认为这次我会做一些代码。
JAKE: Oh, all right.
杰克：哦，好吧。
SURMA: Because it's been you and I'm getting bored of that.
SURMA：因为是你，我对此感到无聊。
So I thought I would talk about something
所以我想我会谈论一些事情
that I've been encountering, and realized,
我一直在遇到并意识到，
that's actually kind of new.
这实际上是新的。
And it's polyfills, which are not new.
它是polyfill，这不是新的。
But conditional loading of polyfills in a world where
但是在有条件的世界中
we all use ES6 modules.
我们都使用ES6模块。
JAKE: All right.
杰克：好吧。
Because it's quite an important thing to do now.
因为这是一件很重要的事情。
Because we're in a situation where some browsers have web
因为我们处于某些浏览器有网络的情况
components, some don't.
组件，有些则没有。
And you don't want to be loading all those polyfills
而且您不想加载所有这些polyfill
for old browsers.
对于旧的浏览器。
SURMA: Because it can be quite big.
SURMA：因为它可能很大。
But also, you don't want to go to the lowest
而且，您也不想走到最低
common denominator all the time, because that's not
一直都是公分母，因为那不是
a great experience for you as a developer.
对于您来说，这是一个很棒的经验。
All right.
好吧。
JAKE: Come on.
杰克：快点。
Show me what you got.
告诉我你得到了什么。
Right.
对。
SURMA: It's not polyfills yet.
SURMA：还不是polyfills。
But for example, let's say I want to use transform streams.
但是例如，假设我要使用转换流。
Personally, I've been loving transform streams.
就个人而言，我一直喜欢转换流。
JAKE: They are amazing, yes.
杰克：太好了，是的。
SURMA: Not only just to do streams, but I actually
SURMA：不仅是做流媒体，而且我实际上
just use them as a FIFO cue.
只需将它们用作FIFO提示即可。
For example, if you have an event handler,
例如，如果您有一个事件处理程序，
and you want to make sure your previous event is completely
并且您想确保之前的活动完全完成
processed before you process the next one,
在处理下一个之前，
just pipe them to a transform stream.
只需将它们传送到转换流即可。
JAKE: Because if you're returning a promise
杰克：因为如果你要兑现诺言
from your transform stream handler,
从您的转换流处理程序中，
it's not going to give you the next one
它不会给你下一个
until all of that's resolved.
直到所有这些都解决了。
SURMA: And it buffers it up until then.
SURMA：并一直缓冲到那时。
So that's actually quite neat.
所以这实际上很整洁。
JAKE: Very clever.
杰克：非常聪明。
Right.
对。
OK.
好。
SURMA: Problem, though.
SURMA：不过有问题。
We have transformed stream in Chrome.
我们已经在Chrome中转换了流。
I think they're just bound to land in Safari.
我认为他们一定会登陆Safari。
They're not in Firefox?
他们不在Firefox中吗？
I should look this up.
我应该查一下。
I don't know.
我不知道。
But basically what I'm saying is the landscape
但基本上我要说的是风景
is uneven in terms of support for transform streams.
在对转换流的支持方面不平衡。
JAKE: Right
杰克：对
SURMA: So what you want to do is load a polyfill.
SURMA：所以您要做的就是加载一个polyfill。
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
SURMA: And so in the olden days, you would just do this, right?
SURMA：所以在过去，您会这样做，对吗？
You would just put a script tag ahead,
您只需将脚本标签放在前面，
and you could be sure that that script would execute
并且您可以确定该脚本将执行
before the other one executes.
在另一个执行之前。
JAKE: Transform stream is fully polyfillable.
杰克：变换流是完全可填充的。
SURMA: Exactly.
苏尔玛：是的。
JAKE: "Pulifillibul."
杰克：“埔里菲布尔。”
SURMA: It's technically completely user-lined.
SURMA：从技术上来说，它完全是用户界面。
But you don't want to load that code usually.
但是您通常不想加载该代码。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
SURMA: So in this case, the polyfill
SURMA：在这种情况下，polyfill
would put their implantation on the global.
将其植入全球。
Maybe even only if it is not already there.
也许即使它还不存在。
So you would use a native implantation
所以你会使用原生植入
because it might be faster.
因为它可能会更快。
And otherwise, it just adds it.
否则，它只会添加它。
And then the transform stream exists,
然后存在转换流，
and you can just use it.
您可以使用它。
Great.
大。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
Brilliant.
辉煌。
SURMA: Problem, now, of course, is it gets old every time.
SURMA：问题是，现在当然是每次都变老了。
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
SURMA: And you might have a browser
SURMA：您可能拥有浏览器
that doesn't need to load that.
不需要加载它。
And it might go--
可能会-
JAKE: Like Chrome right now.
杰克：现在就像Chrome。
Like Safari.
像Safari。
SURMA: And if you can avoid that,
瑟玛：如果您能避免这种情况，
you would want to avoid that.
您可能想要避免这种情况。
JAKE: Excellent.
杰克：太好了。
SURMA: So now let's look into how you do conditional loading.
SURMA：现在让我们看看如何进行条件加载。
And that's where we already started
这就是我们已经开始的地方
looking into importing stuff.
寻找进口的东西。
Because in the olden days, again, you
因为在过去，你又
would probably create a script tag dynamically
可能会动态创建脚本标签
and wait for the unload event.
然后等待卸载事件。
Now we have dynamic import.
现在我们有了动态导入。
JAKE: I think this is something I got wrong
杰克：我认为这是我错了
in a previous episode.
在上一集中。
Because you can use the dynamic import even
因为您甚至可以使用动态导入
in a regular script.
在常规脚本中。
SURMA: Yes, you can.
SURMA：是的，可以。
JAKE: That's very good.
杰克：很好。
SURMA: It's very exciting.
瑟玛：太令人兴奋了。
You don't have to use a module script to use dynamic import.
您无需使用模块脚本即可使用动态导入。
Only for static import.
仅用于静态导入。
So in this case, I'm just checking,
因此，在这种情况下，我只是在检查，
does transform stream exist on self?
转换流是否存在于自身上？
And if that is not the case, time to load the thing.
如果不是这种情况，就该加载东西了。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
So this is a module that's not returning anything.
因此，这是一个不返回任何内容的模块。
SURMA: No.
苏尔玛：不。
It's a polyfill.
这是一个polyfill。
It just attaches to the global.
它只是附属于全球。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
OK.
好。
SURMA: But that's exactly the point.
瑟玛：但这就是重点。
We are now preferring in advocating people to--
我们现在更喜欢提倡人们-
in general, polyfills shouldn't do that.
通常，polyfills不应这样做。
They shouldn't attach themselves to the globals,
他们不应该依赖全球
because then you land in this place
因为那样你就降落在这个地方
where you might be overriding a native implementation that
在这里您可能要覆盖本机实现，
might not be up to date, or it can--
可能不是最新的，或者可以-
there are so many complications.
有这么多的并发症。
JAKE: The whole "smoosh" problem.
杰克：整个“骗局”问题。
SURMA: Exactly.
苏尔玛：是的。
We don't want to have a second "smoosh."
我们不想再有“ smoosh”。
So usually, if you publish a polyfill,
因此，通常，如果您发布一个polyfill，
you use something that exposes just the thing to you.
您使用的东西只会向您展示东西。
And you can decide if you want to attach it to the global
您可以决定是否要将其附加到全局
or handle it yourself.
或自己处理。
JAKE: Brilliant.
杰克：很棒。
SURMA: So instead of a polyfill, you would use a module.
SURMA：因此，您可以使用模块而不是polyfill。
JAKE: Ah.
杰克：啊。
SURMA: Something that doesn't actually modify
SURMA：并未真正修改的内容
the global at all, but just returns something to you
全局的，但只是向您返回了一些东西
that you can use.
您可以使用的。
JAKE: OK.
杰克：好的。
SURMA: And so in this case, we are just importing,
SURMA：在这种情况下，我们只是在导入，
and don't use it.
并且不要使用它。
So in this case, this will still be undefined.
因此，在这种情况下，这仍然是不确定的。
So this pattern doesn't work anymore.
因此，此模式不再起作用。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
Because it's expecting something around here to be returned.
因为期望这里附近的东西会被退回。
And that would be your module.
那将是您的模块。
Right.
对。
OK.
好。
SURMA: So now we have a module that exposes these things.
SURMA：因此，现在我们有了一个暴露这些东西的模块。
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
SURMA: But you can't just attach them to the global
SURMA：但是您不能仅仅将它们附加到全球
because you have to load them ahead every time.
因为您每次都必须提前加载它们。
You have to, at the start of your module,
您必须在模块开始时
you have now to check, does it exist?
您现在要检查，是否存在？
Does it not exist?
它不存在吗？
And if it doesn't exist, hold the entire module
如果不存在，请保留整个模块
until I've loaded the polyfill.
直到我加载了polyfill。
JAKE: Oh, I see.
杰克：哦，我明白了。
SURMA: And then I have to load the module,
SURMA：然后我必须加载模块，
rip it out, and attach it to the global.
撕掉它，并将其附加到全局。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
Because especially if it's third party code,
因为尤其是第三方代码，
you want all it to wait somehow.
您希望所有这些都以某种方式等待。
SURMA: And it gets really weird.
SURMA：真的很奇怪。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
OK.
好。
Yep.
是的
SURMA: So now let's move on to proper modern world ES6
SURMA：现在让我们继续讨论合适的现代世界ES6
modules.
模块。
How could we solve?
我们该如何解决？
So the first version--
第一个版本
JAKE: Bracing for modern JavaScript.
JAKE：支持现代JavaScript。
SURMA: Boom.
苏尔玛：B。
JAKE: Ooh, Look at that modern JavaScript.
杰克：哦，看一下现代的JavaScript。
SURMA: We just turn it into a very, very small two line
SURMA：我们只是将其变成非常小的两行
module that loads the module, attaches it to the global,
加载模块的模块，将其附加到全局模块，
and you depend on this module in every other module
并且您在每个其他模块中都依赖此模块
that uses streams.
使用流。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
And we've avoided the whole--
而且我们避免了整个过程-
I mean, this is still going to be asynchronous
我的意思是，这仍然是异步的
in terms of it's not going to block the main thread.
在这方面，它不会阻塞主线程。
But it's synchronous in terms of that code that comes after it.
但是就其后的代码而言，它是同步的。
SURMA: And so this is a completely valid, completely
瑟玛：这是一个完全有效，完全
acceptable way to go about it.
可接受的解决方法。
Right?
对？
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
SURMA: So this works in the sense
瑟玛：所以这在一定意义上是可行的
that you load the polyfill, and it attaches to the global.
加载polyfill，并将其附加到全局。
And all your code now works for the polyfill if necessary,
现在，您的所有代码现在都可以在需要时用于polyfill了，
but we lost the conditional loading.
但是我们失去了条件加载
JAKE: Ah.
杰克：啊。
Yes.
是。
Of course.
当然。
SURMA: Because conditional loading is not
SURMA：因为没有条件加载
possible with static imports.
静态导入可能。
Because they're static.
因为它们是静态的。
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
That is true.
那是真实的。
SURMA: It's kind of hidden.
苏尔玛：有点隐藏。
And once you think of it, it's like, wait.
一旦想到，就等着。
I cannot do--
我不能做 -
JAKE: Yeah, you can't put an if statement around that.
杰克：是的，您不能在其中加上if语句。
The import has to be sort of top level.
导入必须是顶级的。
SURMA: Either you depend on this module, or you don't.
SURMA：要么依赖此模块，要么不依赖。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
SURMA: But the second you want to do conditional loading,
SURMA：但是第二个您要进行条件加载
you have to go to dynamic import.
您必须进行动态导入。
And then you're back at the problem.
然后您又回到了问题所在。
Because now I have to hold my module
因为现在我必须握住我的模块
until the polyfill is loaded, and that's really weird.
直到加载了polyfill，这真的很奇怪。
JAKE: Do you have--
杰克：你有-
I hope this is going to end with a solution.
我希望这将以解决方案结束。
SURMA: I have a solution.
SURMA：我有一个解决方案。
I don't think it's perfect, but I actually have been using it,
我认为它并不完美，但实际上我一直在使用它，
and it's quite nice.
很好。
Because the second problem with static import is it
因为静态导入的第二个问题是
delays the execution of the module,
延迟模块的执行，
even though you might only need the transform stream
即使您可能只需要转换流
in some specific method.
在某些特定方法中。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
I see.
我懂了。
And that could be a few interactions away,
可能还有一些互动，
or something.
或者其他的东西。
SURMA: Exactly.
苏尔玛：是的。
So you might want to load it at a deferred point,
因此，您可能希望将其加载到延迟的位置，
or even on demand if it's some sort of background task.
甚至按需（如果是某种后台任务）。
So what I've been using is a different approach,
所以我一直在使用另一种方法，
which feels a bit weird, but actually, as a pattern,
感觉有点奇怪，但实际上，作为一种模式，
works really well.
真的很好
JAKE: All right.
杰克：好吧。
SURMA: I'm creating a promise.
苏玛：我正在创造一个诺言。
JAKE: You are.
杰克：你是。
Yes.
是。
SURMA: And so I'm creating a transform stream promise.
SURMA：因此，我正在创建一个转换流承诺。
And that, I can now use an if statement.
而且，我现在可以使用if语句。
And then, if transform stream exists,
然后，如果存在转换流，
I'm just going to return the native transform stream.
我将返回本机转换流。
JAKE: I see.
杰克：我明白了。
SURMA: And if not, I'm going to dynamically load the polyfill,
SURMA：如果没有，我将动态加载polyfill，
and return that one.
并退还那个。
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
SURMA: So now we have a promise that
瑟玛：所以现在我们有一个承诺
will always resolve to a transform stream constructor.
将始终解析为转换流构造函数。
And it might be the native one.
它可能是本地的。
It might be the polyfilled one.
它可能是填充的。
But you don't have to worry about it anymore.
但是您不必再为此担心了。
JAKE: Right.
杰克：对。
SURMA: And that means your module can execute
SURMA：这意味着您的模块可以执行
as fast as possible, or as soon as possible,
尽快或尽快
and will load the code the second you need to.
并在需要的第二秒加载代码。
JAKE: And so this is going to be--
杰克：所以这将会是……
you've got the asynchronous problem back, right?
您又有了异步问题，对不对？
SURMA: Sure.
苏尔玛：好的。
But that is usually--
但这通常是-
this is kind of specific to the point of streams,
这是特定于流的点，
but-- most of the time, streams are in asynchronous context
但是-在大多数情况下，流是在异步上下文中
anyway.
无论如何。
JAKE: That's true.
杰克：是的。
SURMA: So either on the sending side,
SURMA：所以在发送方，
you don't need to worry that it's
您不必担心它是
a promise most of the time, because you can just resolve it
大多数时候都是一个诺言，因为您可以解决它
in line.
排队。
The function can return earlier, and just
该函数可以更早返回，并且仅
wait for this problem to resolve, and then send it,
等待此问题解决，然后将其发送，
because you don't need to worry about it.
因为您不必担心。
On the receiving side, it's asynchronous anyway,
在接收端，它还是异步的，
because it's a stream.
因为是溪流
So you, most of the time, have an async
因此，您大部分时间都处于异步状态
that you can use to await this thing.
您可以用来等待这件事。
JAKE: Excellent.
杰克：太好了。
So this is a pattern that works really well for code
所以这是一种非常适合代码的模式
that you're in control of, right?
你控制的，对不对？
Because you are now using a transform stream
因为您现在正在使用转换流
promise, instead of a transform.
承诺，而不是转变。
If it's for third party code that
如果是第三方代码
is expecting transform to be on the global,
期望转型将在全球范围内进行，
that's when you're going to have to start
那就是你必须开始的时候
delaying the loading of that third party code.
延迟加载该第三方代码。
SURMA: That being said, if you have third party code that
SURMA：话虽如此，如果您有第三方代码
relies on transform streams, something is a little bit
依靠转换流，有点
going wrong, right?
出问题了吧？
JAKE: Oh.
杰克：哦。
I've got mixed feelings about that.
我对此有百感交集。
Because I see what you're saying.
因为我明白你在说什么。
But then you could end up-- if each library is loading
但是，如果每个库都在加载，那么最终可能会失败
a polyfill for transform streams,
用于转换流的polyfill，
you could end up with this problem
你可能会遇到这个问题
where you're loading five libraries that
您要在其中加载五个库
are using transform streams, each
正在使用转换流，每个
loading their own polyfill.
加载自己的polyfill。
Unless they're using exactly the same version.
除非他们使用完全相同的版本。
SURMA: In that sense though, that's
瑟玛：虽然从这个意义上讲，
where you would dynamically load the polyfill,
您将动态加载polyfill的位置
attach it to the global, and then dynamically load
将其附加到全局，然后动态加载
the third party.
第三方。
JAKE: Yes.
杰克：是的。
Exactly.
究竟。
SURMA: And that's because some people might
瑟玛：那是因为有些人可能
be disgusted by this pattern at the bottom, where
对底部的这种模式感到厌恶，
you await something, and immediately call new.
您等待一些事情，然后立即打电话给new。
You can often write in two lines, which might be nicer.
您通常可以写两行，这可能更好。
JAKE: Of course.
杰克：当然。
SURMA: Probably even if will go back and package it
SURMA：即使回去打包
back up, because of what manufacturers do nowadays.
备份，因为现在制造商在做什么。
JAKE: And if you're confident that the polyfill is
杰克：如果您确信polyfill是
feature complete and the spec is settled,
功能齐全，规格已确定，
then this is a point where you could assign it to the global
然后可以在此处将其分配给全局
if you were loading third party code.
如果您正在加载第三方代码。
SURMA: But I feel like the promise
瑟玛：但是我感觉像是承诺
if I constructor pattern is a really nice way of loading
如果我构造函数模式是一种非常好的加载方式
polyfills on demand, ensuring for you to run as much code
按需填充，确保您运行尽可能多的代码
as possible with as little requests
尽可能少的请求
as possible at the start.
一开始就尽可能。
JAKE: And you're loading this ahead of time
杰克：而且您要提前加载
as well, but asynchronously.
同样，但异步。
SURMA: And that's your choice now.
SURMA：这就是您现在的选择。
You can decide when the loading happens.
您可以决定何时加载。
If you're like, actually, I don't
如果你喜欢，实际上，我不会
need to load this right at the start.
首先需要加载此权限。
I can actually load it and request callback,
我实际上可以加载它并请求回调，
you can do that as well.
您也可以这样做。
That' how things work now.
现在事情就是这样。
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
Hulk is back.
绿巨人回来了。
JAKE: (LAUGHING) Hulk is back?
杰克：（笑）绿巨人回来了吗？
That's your normal state?
那是你的正常状态吗？
SURMA: Have you seen my bicep?
瑟玛：你看过我的二头肌吗？
This is, like, made of steel!
就像是钢制的！
JAKE: Made of soy, mate.
杰克：由大豆制成，伴侣。
[LAUGHTER]
[笑声]